[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the plural form of dice?", "correct_answer": "It already is plural", "incorrect_answers": ["Dicess", "Bidice", "Dices"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Etymologists study the history of languages and how the forms and meanings of different words changed.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of the mushroom known as flower-pot parasol and plantpot dapperling?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Purple", "Pink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the cheetah the only animal on land that can turn while running?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the only person to have two movies among the top 15 on the AFI 100 list, written and directed by him?", "correct_answer": "Billy Wilder", "incorrect_answers": ["Alfred Hitchcock", "Frank Capra", "John Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why are recoilless guns recoilless?", "correct_answer": "Their barrels are open at both ends.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are loaded with missiles not cannon balls.", "They are made of  very heavy metals.", "They are not placed on wheels."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Popeyes opened their 1000th restaurant in New Orleans, LA.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What continent is the aardvark native to?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "America", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What beautiful actress voices Juarez in  G-Force?", "correct_answer": "Penelope Cruz", "incorrect_answers": ["Cameron Diaz", "America Ferrera", "Jennifer Lopez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are more than 500,000 craters on the moon that can be seen from Earth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2002, which manufacturer announced the first 3GPP compliant EDGE (Enhanced Data-Rates for GSM Evolution) handset?", "correct_answer": "Nokia", "incorrect_answers": ["Sony Ericsson", "Samsung", "Motorola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is considered to have been the first mall.", "correct_answer": "Isfahan Grand Bazaar", "incorrect_answers": ["The Grand Shoppes at  Kent", "The Magnificante at Toledo", "Tashkent Roayl Bazaar"]}]